Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXI. SYSTEM BOARDS
  - Sub-Series 250-38-E. System Boards. New York Central (Lines East)
    - New York Central (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - New York Central (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1950 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 250-38-W. System Boards. New York Central (Lines West)
    - New York Central (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - New York Central (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - New York Central (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 197, Folder 10)
      January 15, 1957-59.
    - New York Central (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1957 (Box 197, Folder 11)
      1955-January 14, 1957.
    - New York Central (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1954 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - New York Central (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1950 (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - New York Central (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1943 (Box 197a, Folder 1)
    - New York Central (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1930-1932 (Box 197a, Folder 2)
      July 1930-32.
    - New York Central (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1930 (Box 197a, Folder 3)
      1921-June 1930.
  - Sub-Series 250-39. System Boards. Alabama, Tennessee, and Northern
    - Alabama, Tennessee, and Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1951 (Box 197a, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-40. System Boards. Southern Pacific (Texas and Louisiana Department)
    - Southern Pacific (Texas and Louisiana Department) System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 197a, Folder 5)
    - Southern Pacific (Texas and Louisiana Department) System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 197a, Folder 6)
      April 1960-62.
    - Southern Pacific (Texas and Louisiana Department) System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1960 (Box 197a, Folder 7)
      1955-March 1960.
    - Southern Pacific (Texas and Louisiana Department) System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1954 (Box 197a, Folder 8)
    - Southern Pacific (Texas and Louisiana Department) System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1950 (Box 197a, Folder 9)
    - Southern Pacific (Texas and Louisiana Department) System Board of Adjustment, 1936-1943 (Box 197a, Folder 10)
      June 1936-43.
    - Southern Pacific (Texas and Louisiana Department) System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1936 (Box 197a, Folder 11)
      1922-May 1936.
  - Sub-Series 250-41. System Boards. Boston and Albany
    - Boston and Albany System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Boston and Albany System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1959 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Boston and Albany System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1953 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-43. System Boards. Spokane, Portland, and Seattle
    - Spokane, Portland, and Seattle System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1963 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Spokane, Portland, and Seattle System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1951 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-47. System Boards. Chicago and Northwestern
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1952 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-50. System Boards. Hocking Valley
    - Hocking Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1938 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Hocking Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1936 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-51. System Boards. Toledo Terminal
    - Toledo Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1956 (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 250-53. System Boards. Minneapolis and St. Louis
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1961 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1934 (Box 198, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-57. System Boards. Chicago and Northwestern
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1962 (Box 198, Folder 13)
      June 1961-62.
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1963 (Box 198, Folder 14)
      Subject: Appeal Warren W. Menzner
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1963 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1961 (Box 198, Folder 17)
      July 1960-May 1961.
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1960 (Box 199, Folder 1)
      July 1959-June 1960.
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1959 (Box 199, Folder 2)
      January 4, 1958-June 1959.
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1958 (Box 199, Folder 3)
      July 1957-January 3, 1958.
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1957 (Box 199, Folder 4)
      1951-June 1957.
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1950 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1940-1943 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1926-1939 (Box 199, Folder 7)
      May 1926-39.
    - Chicago and Northwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1926 (Box 199, Folder 8)
      1921-April 1926.
  - Sub-Series 250-29. System Boards. Washington Terminal
    - Washington Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1960 (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 250-60. System Boards. Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville
    - Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1961 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1948 (Box 199, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-61. System Boards. Bessemer and Lake Erie
    - Bessemer and Lake Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1960 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Bessemer and Lake Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1942 (Box 199, Folder 13)
      Subject: Appeal H.C. Jones
  - Sub-Series 250-62. System Boards. Erie-Lackawanna
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1959 (Box 199, Folder 14)
      Subject: Schreur deferred salary
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1965-1966 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1957 (Box 200, Folder 4)
      June 1955-June 1957.
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1955 (Box 200, Folder 5)
      August 1951-May 1955.
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1951 (Box 200, Folder 6)
      August 1946-July 1951.
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1946 (Box 200, Folder 7)
      1944-July 1946.
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1943 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1937 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Erie-Lackawanna System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1931 (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-63. System Boards. Hurst Engineering and Construction Company
    - Hurst Engineering and Construction Company System Board of Adjustment, 1958 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 250-65. System Boards. Belt Railway of Chicago
    - Belt Railway of Chicago System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1960 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-66. System Boards. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie
    - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1959 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1952 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-67. System Boards. Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1966 (Box 201, Folder 6)
      1963-April 1966.
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 201, Folder 7)
      April 23, 1960-62.
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 8)
      March 1960-April 22, 1960.
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1960 (Box 201, Folder 9)
      June 1958-February 1960.
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1958 (Box 201, Folder 10)
      May 1957-May 1958.
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1957 (Box 201, Folder 11)
      August 1955-April 1957.
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1955 (Box 202, Folder 1)
      August 1951-July 1955.
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1951 (Box 202, Folder 2)
      1948-July 1951.
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1947 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1946 (Box 202, Folder 4)
      Subject: Charges against R.J. Lackey
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1933 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-69. System Boards. Southern
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1966 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1963 (Box 202, Folder 10)
      August 1960-63. Subject: Appeal V.W. Hague
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1961 (Box 202, Folder 11)
      July 1960-61.
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 202, Folder 12)
      April 1957-59.
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1957 (Box 202, Folder 13)
      July 1955-March 1957.
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1955 (Box 202, Folder 14)
      1952-June 1955.
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1951 (Box 203, Folder 1)
      July 1949-51.
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1949 (Box 203, Folder 2)
      1947-June 1949.
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1946 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1943 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1932-1938 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1920-1931 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1941 (Box 203, Folder 7)
      June 16-18, 1941. Subject: Minutes
    - Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1939 (Box 203, Folder 8)
      June 12-13, 1939. Subject: Minutes
  - Sub-Series 250-70. System Boards. Chicago, Peoria, and St. Louis
    - Chicago, Peoria, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1927 (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 250-72. System Boards. International and Great Northern
    - International and Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1955 (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-74. System Boards. Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1960 (Box 203, Folder 13)
      November 1957-June 1960.
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1957 (Box 203, Folder 14)
      1954-October 1957.
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1932-1950 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1930 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-76. System Boards. Chicago Great Western
    - Chicago Great Western System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1951 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-77. System Boards. El Paso Southwestern
    - El Paso Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1926 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-78. System Boards. Colorado and Southern
    - Colorado and Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1961 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Colorado and Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1954 (Box 204, Folder 7)
      March 1947-54.
    - Colorado and Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1945 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Colorado and Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1947 (Box 204, Folder 9)
      1946-February 1947.
  - Sub-Series 250-79. System Boards. Kentucky and Indiana
    - Kentucky and Indiana System Board of Adjustment, 1924-1961 (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-80. System Boards. Kansas City, Mexico, and Orient
    - Kansas City, Mexico, and Orient System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1928 (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-81. System Boards. Kansas City Southern
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1964 (Box 204, Folder 12)
      March 1961-64.
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1961 (Box 204, Folder 13)
      April 1955-February 1961.
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1955 (Box 204, Folder 14)
      1951-March 1955.
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1950 (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1944 (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1943 (Box 204, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 250-82. System Boards. Florida East Coast
    - Florida East Coast System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1939 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Florida East Coast System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1927 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-83. System Boards. Duluth and Iron Range
    - Duluth and Iron Range System Board of Adjustment, 1921 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-84. System Boards. Missouri Pacific
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1959 (Box 205, Folder 7)
      May 1958-59.
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 205, Folder 8)
      April 5, 1956-April 1958.
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1956 (Box 205, Folder 9)
      1955-April 4, 1956.
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1956 (Box 205, Folder 10)
      1956 February 16. Subject: Minutes
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1956 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1954 (Box 205, Folder 12)
      July 1951-54.
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1951 (Box 205, Folder 13)
      1939-June 1951.
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1925-1936 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1924 (Box 205, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 250-86. System Boards. Trunk Line Freight Inspection Bureau
    - Trunk Line Freight Inspection Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1925 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 250-89. System Boards. Los Angeles and Salt Lake
    - Los Angeles and Salt Lake System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1934 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-90. System Boards. Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1954 (Box 206, Folder 4)
      1949-May 1954.
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1948 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1922 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-91. System Boards. Western Maryland
    - Western Maryland System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1962 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Western Maryland System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1957 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Western Maryland System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1953 (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 250-92. System Boards. Toledo, St. Louis, and Western
    - Toledo, St. Louis, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1925 (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-95. System Boards. Peoria and Pekin Union
    - Peoria and Pekin Union System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1958 (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-96. System Boards. Rutland Railroad
    - Rutland Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1960 (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-97. System Boards. Norfolk and Western
    - Norfolk and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1962 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Norfolk and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Norfolk and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1959 (Box 206a, Folder 1)
      Subject: Appeal Lodge No. 1090
    - Norfolk and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1957 (Box 206a, Folder 2)
      September 1954-June 1957.
    - Norfolk and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1954 (Box 206a, Folder 3)
      1951-August 1954.
    - Norfolk and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1950 (Box 206a, Folder 4)
      June 1946-50.
    - Norfolk and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1946 (Box 206a, Folder 5)
      1939-May 1946.
    - Norfolk and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1925 (Box 206a, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-98. System Boards. Chicago and Eastern Illinois
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1962 (Box 206a, Folder 7)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1945 (Box 206a, Folder 8)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois System Board of Adjustment, 1940-1943 (Box 206a, Folder 9)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois System Board of Adjustment, 1942 (Box 206a, Folder 10)
      1942 February 26. Subject: Trials of B. Berg, et. al.
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1939 (Box 206a, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-99. System Boards. Boston and Maine
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 206b, Folder 1)
      May 9, 1960-62.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1960 (Box 206b, Folder 2)
      1959-May 8, 1960.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1958 (Box 206b, Folder 3)
      May 8, 1957-58.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1957 (Box 206b, Folder 4)
      1954-May 7, 1957.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1953 (Box 206b, Folder 5)
      May 1952-53.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1949 (Box 206b, Folder 6)
      April 1947-49.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1947 (Box 206b, Folder 7)
      May 1946-March 1947.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1946 (Box 206b, Folder 8)
      1945-April 1946.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1943-1944 (Box 206b, Folder 9)
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1942-1944 (Box 206b, Folder 10)
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1943 (Box 207, Folder 1)
      Subject: Appeal Henry P. Cronin
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1943 (Box 207, Folder 2)
      Subject: Complaints Henry P. Cronin
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1932 (Box 207, Folder 3)
      Subject: Appeal General Office Lodges
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1941 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1928-1933 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1925-1927 (Box 207, Folder 6)
      April 1925-27.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1925 (Box 207, Folder 7)
      December 1923-April 1925.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1927 (Box 207, Folder 8)
      November 1922-September 1927.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1952 (Box 208, Folder 1)
      July 1950-April 1952.
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1950 (Box 208, Folder 2)
      January-June 1950.
  - Sub-Series 250-100. System Boards. Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1964 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1959 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1952 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1945 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1933 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 250-101. System Boards. Atlanta Joint Terminal
    - Atlanta Joint Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1927-1954 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-102. System Boards. Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1957 (Box 208, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-103. System Boards. Long Island
    - Long Island System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1962 (Box 208, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-104. System Boards. Central Railroad of New Jersey
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1962 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1957 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1950 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1940 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-107. System Boards. Houston Belt and Terminal Company
    - Houston Belt and Terminal Company System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1935 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 250-108. System Boards. Chicago and Western Indiana
    - Chicago and Western Indiana System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1968 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Chicago and Western Indiana System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 209, Folder 9)
      June 1959-62.
    - Chicago and Western Indiana System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1959 (Box 209, Folder 10)
      1922-May 1959.
  - Sub-Series 250-110. System Boards. Midland Valley
    - Midland Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1969 (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-112. System Boards. Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago, and St. Louis
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1959 (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1947 (Box 209, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 250-113. System Boards. Nickel Plate System
    - Nickel Plate System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1961 (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - Nickel Plate System Board of Adjustment, 1932-1940 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Nickel Plate System Board of Adjustment, 1920-1931 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-115. System Boards. Oregon Short Line
    - Oregon Short Line System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1934 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-116. System Boards. Oregon-Washington Railroad and Navigation Company